ironsocket.com 2017-04-17

# IronSocket - Privacy Policy

Effective Date: August 8, 2014

### Overview

We are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. We limit what information we collect to the minimum needed to provide our service, manage your account, and to protect ourselves from fraud and abuse. In a nutshell:

We **DO NOT LOG** or record in any manner the content you access while using our Services.  
We **DO NOT USE** your information for purposes other than those to which you have consented.  
We **DO NOT SELL** or trade personal information for commercial purposes.

We do not share personally identifiable information regarding your account except when compelled by legal actions valid under the laws of Hong Kong.

### Introduction

This Privacy Policy (the "Policy"), together with any other documents referred to in it, sets out the basis on which information we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us. It also describes the actions you can take to access this information and request that the Company correct or delete it. This Policy applies to your use of IronSocket.com, its blog and social media sites (collectively, the "Site") and describes the information we may collect about visitors as well as subscribers to our services, including but not limited to downloadable proprietary software applications, HTTP proxy services, DNS proxy services, SOCKS5 proxy services, virtual private network services and other services (the "Services") which are owned and operated by Pusa and Daga Hong Kong Limited (collectively, the "Company" "we" "our" or "us").

### Consent

Please read this Policy carefully before you use our Site or Services. By using our Site, you affirmatively accept this Policy and agree to abide by its terms and conditions. If you do not agree to this Policy, do not use the Site and Services.

**THE SITE AND SERVICES ARE NOT OFFERED FOR USE BY PERSONS UNDER 18 YEARS OF AGE.** If you are under 18 years of age, please do not use the Site or the Services. If you are a parent or guardian and believe that your minor has provided personal information to us, please contact us so that we can delete the information.

Our Terms of Use, incorporated herein by reference, including the limitations on liability, apply to this Policy. You can read it here: https://ironsocket.com/terms-of-use

### Information Collected

When you Visit the Site, we collect the following information:  

  * Your IP address, browser type, operating system, and time of visit;
  * The pages and content you viewed while browsing the Site; and
  * Information about how you arrived on the Site such as, the referring site, advertisement information, keyword search phrase, etc.

We use this data to understand usage trends and to determine the effectivity of our marketing.

Upon Registration and Use of the Site, we additionally collect the following limited information:

  * Your provided email address, and password;
  * Any referral or coupon codes used;
  * Details about your subscription choices;
  * Details about your payment such as payment type, transaction ID, and limited transaction data provided by the payment processor used; and
  * All customer communications and files received via email, online chat, or web form submission such as our Contact Us form, or through the use of our Ticket System.

Upon Use of the Services, we additionally collect the following session information:  

  * Time and date of the session connection and disconnection;
  * The IP address used for the session and which server was connected to; and
  * A numerical representation showing total bytes transferred per session;

We use this data to manage your account, to provide the Services, and to prevent fraud and abuse. This session information is retained for a limited period of time, typically 72 hours, after which it is purged from our servers.

### Information Disclosure

We may share aggregate statistical date and other forms of non-Personally Identifiable Information with non-affiliated third parties for advertising, marketing or research purposes.

We MAY disclose certain limited information about you to third parties (i) in the event of a reorganization of our business, (ii) in order to fulfill the Services, (iii) as required to comply with law enforcement where subpoenas, warrants, or other legal documents have been provided which are valid under Hong Kong jurisdiction, and (iv) to protect the Company. In a nutshell:

  * _Business Transfers_. We may disclose your information to an acquiring company if we are acquired by or merged with another company, or if all or some of our assets are transferred to another company, or as part of a bankruptcy proceeding;
  * _Service Providers_. We may disclose your information to third party service providers who provide services on our behalf, such as processing payments, hosting our Site, and sending email messages for us. Our service providers receive only the information they need to perform their designated functions, and are not permitted to use or disclose this information for their own marketing or other purposes. We are not responsible for any third party payment provider handling your transaction. Please refer to the third party payment provider's privacy policy to see how they use your data;
  * _Legal Process_. The company cooperates fully with law enforcement agencies but only discloses user information when required to do so subject to subpoenas, warrants and legal processes valid under Hong Kong jurisdiction;
    * The extent of disclosure varies greatly based upon the specific Services accessed by the user, the frequency of activity by the user, and the territory of the server(s) to which the user connected;
    * The Company cannot (by system design) disclose IP addresses of websites visited or information about applications, services and websites accessed by any users while connected to our virtual private network service because we DO NOT log or store this information; and
  * _To Protect IronSocket_. In order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to anyone's safety, or violations of our Terms or this Policy, or to exercise or defend legal claims or otherwise protect IronSocket in litigation.

### Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies

We may use or engage tracking technologies, such as cookies and pixels, like many organizations, to better understand user behavior and to improve our services. Web browsers are typically setup to accept cookies; however each browser typically has options that let you control what cookies are accepted, sent or refused.

We use both session and persistent cookies in meaningful ways to provide our Services and to improve the quality of our product. Some of these ways include, but are not limited to:

  * Allowing our system to uniquely identify you while you are logged in to your account;
  * To identify which site, or affiliate may have referred you to the Site; and
  * To track aggregate and statistical information about behaviors on the Site;

We also may make use of third party tracking pixels used by advertising or analytical partners. Some such partners include, but are not limited to:  

  * _Google Analytics_. Used to track statistical information such as page visits and traffic source information allowing us to improve the performance and quality of the Site. For more information please visit: <http://www.google.com/analytics/learn/privacy.html>
  * _Google Advertising_. Used to track conversions from advertisements on the Google Search and Google Display network. For more information please visit: <http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/>

Third party pixels and content may make use of cookies. We do not have access or control over these third party cookies and this Policy does not cover the use of third party cookies.

For more detailed information about cookies, please visit <http://aboutcookies.org/>.

### Security Measures

We use many industry standard security measures to protect your Personally Identifiable Information (PII) from loss, theft, misuse or unauthorized access or disclosure or destruction. These measures include, but are not limited to:  

  * All information you provide is stored on secure servers;
  * We use MFA (multi-factor authentications) processes whenever appropriate;
  * We use high levels of encryption, access controls, security keys, and passwords;
  * All information is stored in electronic formats, securely in our databases and servers;
  * All employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices; and
  * Access to Personally Identifiable Information (PII) is restricted to those who need to know such information to perform their job functions. Despite our efforts, no data security methods guarantee 100% protection. We do not promise and cannot guarantee that your personal information can never be viewed and/or used by others.

### Marketing Emails

Our Marketing emails and newsletters offer helpful information, service updates and may include promotional offers for our services. You may unsubscribe from such mailings at any time by emailing us at [unsubscribe@ironsocket.com](mailto:unsubscribe@ironsocket.com) from the address that you no longer wish to receive mailings to.

### International Transfer

Any information collected by the Company may be transferred, stored and processed in any country in which the Company or its affiliates, subsidiaries, or agents maintain facilities. By using the Site or Services you consent to any such transfer, storage, and processing of information outside of your country.

### Access to Information

We believe in your right to know and review and Personally Identifiable Information (PII) the Company has collected and stored about you. Your right of access can be exercised by sending an e-mail to [legal@pdcontact.com](mailto:legal@pdcontact.com). Requests may be subject to a fee of USD $20.00 to cover the costs of gathering and providing you the data.

### Accountability

Should you have concerns about how your information is handled, or have any questions about our privacy policy, please contact us at [legal@pdcontact.com](mailto:legal@pdcontact.com).

### Changes to this Policy

We may change this Policy from time to time, without prior notice to you, consistent with applicable privacy laws and principles. If we do so, we will post a new effective date for this Policy. Your continued use of the Site or Services constitutes your acceptance of the then-effective Policy.

### Contact Information

Pusa and Daga Hong Kong Limited  
Suite A, 14th Floor  
Gaylord Commercial Building  
114-120 Lockhart Road  
Wan Chai, Hong Kong

Attention: [legal@pdcontact.com](mailto:legal@pdcontact.com)
